Welcome back. You're
cruising right
along into your next topic.
In this section of the course,
we'll teach you all about how to
manage quality and meet
quality standards.
You'll also learn about
quality assurance
and quality control.
We'll take a look at
continuous improvement and
how to use data-driven
frameworks such
as DMAIC and PDCA
in order to work toward
continuous improvements.
You'll also learn how to
conduct retrospectives.
These will help you reflect on
the successes and
setbacks of a project.
Finally, you'll learn about
the importance of
maintaining a positive,
blameless tone
throughout the process.
Are you ready to jump right in?
Let's start with
quality management.
I'll meet you in the next video.